<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>HERE</title>
    <link href="https://shoobieshoobie.github.io/here/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://shoobieshoobie.github.io/here" />
    <updated>2024-09-16T23:01:16-07:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Shoob</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://shoobieshoobie.github.io/here</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Passions</title>
        <author>
            <name>Shoob</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://shoobieshoobie.github.io/here/passions/index.html"/>
        <id>https://shoobieshoobie.github.io/here/passions/index.html</id>
            <category term="Philosophy 404"/>

        <updated>2024-09-16T23:01:16-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    I've found that nothing more in life drives me than fleeting passions. I've needed a way to centralize the things that excite me. I enjoy sharing with others what I'm up to and the things I'm engaging in lately. Social media sites like Facebook, Instagram,&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>I've found that nothing more in life drives me than fleeting passions. I've needed a way to centralize the things that excite me. I enjoy sharing with others what I'm up to and the things I'm engaging in lately. Social media sites like Facebook, Instagram, TikTok, etc. have all become too overwhelming and too focused on generating money. I've started blogs in the past, I'm not sure why I think this one will be any different? Maybe because I'm hoping to encourage my friends to create their own little hubs on the internet.</p>
<p>Or maybe house is a better word. I've started thinking of this little web project as a digital home where each page is a different room. I can decorate it the way I want and include whatever content I'd like. I can even limit who has access.</p>
<p>I think in the past I've expected whatever blogs I have started to grow beyond my immediate circle. But this time around, my focus is solely on communicating to all of you who I already know. My plan is to update this site at least a couple of times a week.</p>
<p>I'm exhausted by how many ideas I generate return to the idea of getting money. I mostly just want to create things with other people and by myself. I hope that by using this site, I can not only share what's going on and what I'm reading and what I'm interested in lately but also remind myself of what I want to focus on, what projects I'm working on, and what my long term goals are.</p>
<p>It's been a long time since I've done any sort of blogging and I've done very little writing in general in a while, so I'm substantially out of practice. I just wanted to get something out there to share. </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
